你得试试这块起司蛋糕
我不是那么喜欢吃甜食…
我的天啊，它好香浓
那是我吃过最棒的起司蛋糕!
你在哪里买到它?
我回家时它就已经放在门口了 有人把它寄给我们
收件人不是你
收件人是楼下的布雷曼太大!
小偷!
我没看收件人姓名就打开了盒子…
盒子已经打开了就无法退还!
为什么? 因为它太好吃了
你偷了这个起司蛋糕，那是不对的
不，没关系的 因为布雷曼太大会免费再收到一个
那可是双赢的局面
唯一的输家是大型起司蛋糕店…
“小妈妈的面包店”
我觉得好难过
我是个大坏蛋
对不起，你说什么?
S07E11 起司蛋糕
我得走了，我今天工作很忙
你们知道我怎么会昏迷不醒吗?
今天他们要帮我做检查 结果发现我没有脑死
所以…
聪明先生
没有脑死的是我演的角色
菲比，今晚的事没取消吧?
当然 八点见
什么东西八点见?
我们约好吃晚餐，我们大约一个月会约一次去讨论你们的事
哇，我真的不知道
我能说你今天看起来很漂亮吗?
那当然
明天你要租辆车一起开过去吗?
你在说什么? 芬妮表妹的婚礼
你被邀请了?
不
我的天啊，我不敢相信
我以为他们只邀请了爸跟妈
七岁到九岁，芬妮跟我形影不离
或许九岁后，芬妮交了新朋友
你要交些新朋友吗?
或许这只是个误会 我打电话去问雪若阿姨
或许他们邀请你了 只是请贴寄丢了
你可以打电话告诉她，我们小时候…
她的宝贝芬妮好几次想脱光我的衣服
要不是我阻止了她，她也结不了婚
她也想脱我的衣服
我以前会帮葛兰表弟脱衣服
乔瑟夫法兰西斯崔比亚尼你回家了吗?
我想他还没有回家，怎么了?
我得告诉你，瑞秋凯伦葛林
我跟乔伊有约 他留了这张字条给我
菲比，我没办法赴约 我有约会，待会再谈
大爹地
大爹地? 那是我们之间的匿称
你们为什么不试试“弗朗西斯”?
弗朗西斯这名字比钱德酷 不是吗?
你知道什么样的匿称不会跟别人重覆吗? “罗斯原子超人”
乔瑟夫法兰西斯回来了!
等一下，你干嘛叫我的全名?
我留了字条给你
那不是放我鸽子的好理由
如果你有机会上床 当然可以取消跟朋友的约会
他说的对，这是规则
真的? 是的，我听到的就是那些
我从来投机会实施规则
无法接受这种事，我们约好后 我期待你地会出现
我不是你泡到马子前打发时间的代替品
男女朋友来来去去但朋友是一辈子的
我真的很抱歉 我不知道这对你来说那么重要
喔，它的确很重要
我可以弥补吗?
对不起
明天晚上一起吃饭吧？ 我会自己付钱
好吧，你说服了我
既然你站在那边，拿罐啤酒给“罗斯原子超人”吧?
“罗斯…”它又回来了?
又有起司蛋糕
他们又把它送到这里来
把它送到楼下去，那有什么问题?
我不知道该怎么说再见
你是认真的吗?
两天前我们吃掉一个蛋糕 你还想再吃?
噢，我已经忘记它的味道了
它是起司蛋糕，它很好吃
它又香又浓，酥酥的饼干…
还有非常浓郁…
但不油腻的奶油起司
我的嘴巴全是口水
你知道吗? 忘了它，我们只是饿了
我们没有吃午餐，所以头昏脑胀
我们去吃午餐，忘了那个起司蛋糕吧
我们得把它还回去，才不会被诱惑
你要去哪里吃午餐? 芝加哥小妈妈面包店
梅尔托尔梅死了（最著名爵士歌王）
乔伊，那是一年前的报纸
那表示山姆古迪商店（音乐CD连锁店）的大特卖结束了
我终于收到雪若阿姨的回音…
很明显地这不是误会
婚礼现场座位有限…
座位有限? 我是个瘦皮猴!
对，但是她不知道
我是说上次她看到你…
你会把婚礼用的小椅子压垮
“座位有限”那真是个烂借口
那不是她不邀请我的原因
那有什么大不了的呢? 我没办法观礼，只能去吃喜酒
如果这能让你觉得开心一点琼安和我只会去亮个相…
我们会提早离开，以示抗议
琼安? 对，她是我的女伴
她是语言系的助教，又高又漂亮
虽然有些人说，别挑太魁梧的女孩
等一下，你收到的喜贴是“请携伴参加”?
我没有被邀请，你却可以“携伴参加”?
对不起，我真的得解释罗斯的行为
我想规则也适用在这里
因为他有机会跟魁梧女人上床…
她没有那么魁梧
兄弟，我见过她．她真的很魁梧
等一下，你得带我去
我不能放琼安鸽子
为什么? 你没有听到吗?
她是语言系的助教
她们很辣
你到底为什么想去?因为…
她是我表妹
我们是一起长大的
我们是家人，你知道吗？ 对我来说那很重要
好吧，我带你去
我去打电话给琼安
那真的是太棒了
家人应该要出席的
这是她的婚礼 她一生中最快乐的日子
我们等着瞧吧
谢谢你请我吃午餐
等一下，我以为你付了钱
很明显的 我们不必再掏钱买食物了
我没有看错吧? 它还在那里
布雷曼太大一定是出去了
她可能出城去了或许几月后才会回来
到时候蛋糕一定坏了 不能让她回来看到坏掉的起司蛋糕
她可能会中毒死掉我不希望发生那种事
我们是在保护她
我们把它拿走，但是快一点
为什么? 我听到她在里面走动的声音
快走…
你认为婚礼上穿白色花边衣服不合适吗
是的太好了
天啊，是大卫
谁? 那个科学家大卫
我爱上的那个大卫
他到俄国去，伤了我的心，大卫
我的天啊!
只要一直念某人的名字那个人就会转过身来
菲比
大卫
你在做什么? 你不是在俄国吗?
我到城里来开会
天啊，你看起来美得出奇
噢…
对
你也看起来也很棒 你剪了头发吗?
对，我大概剪了二十次
听着，我得跟你坦诚一件事
我希望能在这里遇到你
我不知道该不该打电话给你我只会在城里待几天…
我不想打扰你的生活
我真的想见你…
但我不知道你要不要见我
我当然想见你，我常常想到你
真的吗? 因为我也常常想到你
明斯克有一座雕像让我常常想起你
事实上那是列宁的雕像…
但有些角度…
总之，今晚你想跟我共进晚餐吗?
好
哦，不!
什么? 我不能
我不敢相信，我有约了明天可以吗?
不，再过几小时我就得离开 我得赶回去
听着，下次你到明斯克…
菲比，我能跟你谈一谈吗?
你在做什么?
我跟乔伊有约
所以呢? 他会谅解的
不，他不会的，那根本不是重点
我教训他不该见色忘友
现在只因为可能是我真爱的人…
明天就要回俄国去…
我就应该改变我的想法?
我应该改变我的想法!
不，如果失去了原则那么我什么都不会有
你太有说服力了
或许我可以赶快跟乔伊吃完晚餐 然后九点跟大卫见面
我的天啊，那真的是太棒了!
我吃饱了 但我知道如果我现在停下来
我会后梅
嘿，你们在吃什么?
噢，那是…
豆腐蛋糕，你要吃一点吗?
今晚你要做什么?
兄弟
对不起
我跟菲比有约
真的? 莫妮卡说她九点有约会
什么? 今晚? 莫妮卡是那么说的
她教训了我一顿却同时约了我和她的男伴
她想草草解决大爹地
现在如果请你…兄弟，兄弟!
如果我现在脱下裤子你会什么感觉?
就像你表弟格林
好了，我们的位置应该是这一桌
座位有限，我的天啊
我们来看看谁被邀请了
嗨，我是莫妮卡盖勒
你们跟新人是什么关系？ 我是芬妮以前的同事
以前的同事，以前
我是她的亲戚却没有被邀请
我是她的血亲，血
别在陌生人面前提到“血”
从7岁到9岁，我们就不可分离 我甚至没被邀!
那你为什么在这里?
和我哥哥约会 嘿，我有约会，知道吗
简．特德斯基，语言学者
你呢? 你和快乐的新人什么关系?
我们是他们的大学同学
现在是他们的邻居
好吧，你还够格
你会喜欢上简的，她非常开心
看那边!她的背影就像那样 不是很魁梧，对吧?
乔伊，该点菜了
我不喜欢这张桌子 也许我们又要走了
不．就留在这里．对不起我们要点菜了
我不在这里工作
那你就不该走来走去嘛
你们要点菜了吗? 是的
我要沙拉，特调酱汁给我水就好了
你呢? 先生
对，慢烤鲑鱼…
那到底有多慢呢?
它已经烤好了
那么我不要，麻烦你再告诉我一次今日特餐
我们已经听了三次
有烤肋排，鬼头刀鱼跟特制龙虾饺子
事实上我们没有饺子了 那我们得重来一次
你知道吗? 菲比之前你说的话是对的
朋友太重要了
对，我很聪明，我知道
你知道我想做什么吗?
什么? 我想花时间跟你长谈
你知道吗? 告诉我多一点人生道理
可以点菜了吗? 是的
我要点龙虾饺子
天啊，乔伊，这得花一辈子的时问
干嘛这么急呢? 噢…
我有个约会
它非常重要
怎么说?
噢…
我约了一个男人
你约了男人? 不，你一定弄错了 因为你不能跟男人约会…
同时又跟朋友吃饭
别让我觉得内疚
不，我就是要那么做
我跟那个女孩出去你让我觉得非常内疚
好像我做了什么可怕的事 现在你也那么做
才怪，这完全不一样
我跟大卫有约你还记得科学家大卫吗
对我来说他非常特别
那晚我约的女孩也很特别 她也是个科学家
是吗? 她高中毕业
随便啦，你知道吗?
他只会在这里待四小时 我得去见他
好吧 对
你还在这里做什么? 我说过了，龙虾饺子
我正要离开，我以为你不会来了
我绝不会错过这次约会
我很高兴你来了
你是个绅士
来吧，到我家去
你想一个人独吞起司蛋糕?
只要你现在能吹出口哨 我就给你一百块
你怎么可以不管我一个人独吞？ 你会怎么做呢?
告诉莫妮卡或乔伊? 不 你得把一切告诉他们
我们是甜点小偷，我们犯了法
我不能让你跟起司蛋糕独处
我先发现它的，我要把它拿回来
什么? 不 对
你以为我就能相信你吗?
不，我们平分它
那不公平，你已经吃掉一点了
我想莫妮卡一定想知道…
你说她做的起司蛋糕“又干又粗”
我们要用什么来切蛋糕?
好了，挑一块
这块比较大
但这块饼干比较多
或者我该量一下…
快挑一块
好吧，我挑那一块 那一块比较小
好了，拿去吧
好好享受你的蛋糕吧 我的朋友，因为大势己定
我不会跟你分，或跟你换 别哭着跑来找我…
如果一下子就把蛋糕吃完了
你要给我一点蛋糕吗?不
我不会跟你分或跟你换别哭着跑来找我
我要坐在这里花一整天好好享用我的蛋糕
我要坐在走廊上吃我的…
罗斯，甜心!
嘿，米莉阿姨
这个婚礼很温馨吧? 没错
她每次都亲嘴巴!
为什么? 为什么要亲嘴巴?
芬妮在那边 她看到我一定会很高兴吧
你得乖乖的，好吗?
我不是带你来欺负她
芬妮把你的《花花公子》拿给妈妈看
那个死小孩
莫妮卡!
什么…?
我在这里做什么? 你看到我很讶异吗
罗斯带我来的，你还喜欢吗?
芬妮，恭喜
你邀请我的家人却不邀请我，为什么?
你为什么不希望我来? 我做了什么?
史都华!
我相信你认识我丈夫
问题应该是，你把上了“谁”
我讨厌这样，但我得走了
我不能错过飞机
我敢说下一班飞注明斯克的飞机是在．，
七月
那真的好窝心，它是什么意思?
“请帮我把杯子洗干挣”
我不常离开实验室
我以为它有别的意思
对，事实上，我想说…
那个
我想或许我不该说，因为…
我得离开
不，你说的对，别说
但我真的那么想
我也是
再见，菲比
现在不是时候，乔伊 明天你可以骂我
等一下，不，菲比，我不会骂你
我只是开始想到你跟大卫…
我记得他第一次离开时你有多难过
菲比，过来
你还好吧? 不，我一点都不好
我唯一喜欢的男人要去明斯克…
或许我永远都不会再见到他
你可以去看他
对，你以为他们会给我护照
有什么我可以帮忙的吗? 什么都行
喔…
如果你可以比他先蒸馏出副原子粒子．
他就可以回来了
我可以试试看
你看! 有一小块没有沾到地板
别越界! 快点!
好了，我们要吃什么?
等一下，我忘了拿披肩。好吧，我在这里等你
我不能回去! 为什么?
你看到期图亚特盯着我吗？ 他可能还想要我
我的天哪 进去帮我拿!
好吧，等着
嗨，甜心! 你要走了吗?
喔…亲阿姨一下，快点
为什么? 为什么要亲嘴巴?
You have got to try this cheesecake.
You know, I'm not that much
of a sweet tooth...
Oh, my God, it's so creamy!
That's the best
cheesecake I've ever had!
Where did you get this?
It was at the front door when I got
home. Somebody sent it to us.
This isn't addressed to you.
This is addressed
to Mrs. Braverman downstairs!
Thief!
I didn't read the box
before I opened it...
...and you can't return a box
after you opened it!
- Why not?
- Because it's too delicious!
You stole this cheesecake.
That's wrong.
No, it'll be okay because Mrs. Braverman
will send for a free one.
That way, we all win.
The only losers are the
big cheesecake conglomerate...
..."Mama's Little Bakery."
I feel terrible.
I'm a horrible, horrible person.
I'm sorry, what?
S07E11 The One With All The Cheesecakes
I should get going. Big day at work.
You know how I'm in a coma?
Today they do a test on me and it
turns out I'm not brain-dead.
So...
Mr. Smarty Pants.
It's just my character
that's not brain-dead.
Pheebs, still on for tonight?
- Absolutely.
- I'll see you at 8.
What's at 8?
Dinner. We get together about once
a month to discuss the rest of you.
Wow! Did not know that.
May I say how lovely you look today?
Duly noted.
So for tomorrow, do you want to
rent a car and drive down together?
- What are you talking about?
- Cousin Frannie's wedding.
You were invited?
No.
Oh, my God, I can't believe this.
I thought only Mom and Dad
were invited.
From the ages of 7 to 9,
Frannie and I were inseparable.
Maybe since the age of 9,
Frannie's made some new friends.
Do you wanna make some new friends?
It's probably just a mistake.
Let me call Aunt Cheryl.
Maybe you are invited and the
invitation got lost in the mail.
You call her and tell her
that when we were kids...
...her precious Frannie
tried to undress me several times.
If I hadrt stopped her, there
wouldn't be a wedding to go to.
She tried to undress me too.
I used to undress my cousin Glenn.
Joseph Francis Tribbiani,
are you home yet?
I think he's still out.
What's wrong?
I'll tell you, Rachel Karen Greene.
I had plans with Joey,
and he left me this note.
"Pheebs, can't make it.
Got a date. Talk to you later.
Big Daddy."
- "Big Daddy"?
- That's a nickname we were trying.
Why didn't you guys try "Francis"?
Francis is a cooler name than Chandler,
isn't it?
You know what nickname
never caught on? "The Ross-a-tron."
Here's Joseph Francis!
Wait, what are you
middle-naming me for?
I left you a note.
That doesn't give you the
right to ditch me!
You can cancel plans with friends
if there's a possibility for sex.
He's right. That is the rule.
- Really?
- Well, that's what I hear.
I've never gotten a chance
to actually employ the rule.
I don't accept it. When we make
plans, I expect you to show up.
I'm not a way to kill time
till you meet someone better.
Boyfriends and girlfriends will
come and go, but this is for life.
I'm so sorry. I had no idea
it would bother you this much.
Well, it does.
Well, can I make it up to you?
I'm sorry.
How about dinner tomorrow night?
I'll pay for myself.
Okay, you wore me down.
While you're over there, how
about a beer for "The Ross-a-tron"?
"Ross..." Is that back?
The other cheesecake came.
They delivered it here again.
Just bring it downstairs.
What's the problem?
I can't seem to say goodbye.
Are you serious?
We ate an entire cake
two days ago and you want more?
Well, I've forgotten
what it tastes like.
It was cheesecake. It was fine.
It had a buttery, crumbly,
graham cracker crust...
...with a very rich...
...yet light cream cheese filling.
Wow, my whole mouth
just filled with saliva.
Know what? Forget it.
We're just hungry.
We haven't had lunch.
We're just lightheaded.
So let's go have lunch
and forget about the cheesecake.
We'll drop it off
so we're not tempted.
- Where do you want to eat?
- Mama's Little Bakery, Chicago.
Mel Torme died.
Joey, that paper's like a year old.
Does that mean the Sam Goody's sale
is over?
So I finally heard back
from Aunt Cheryl...
...and apparently it wasrt a mistake.
There's limited seating...
Limited seating? I am just
one tiny person!
Yeah, but she doesn't know that.
I mean, the last time she saw you...
...you'd have turned one of those
little wedding chairs into kindling.
"Limited seating."
That's such a lame excuse.
That's not the reason
she's not inviting me.
What's the big deal? I wasrt invited
to the ceremony, just the reception.
If it makes you feel any better, Joan
and I will just make an appearance...
...and then we'll leave early
as a sign of protest.
- Joan?
- Yeah, my date.
Assistant professor in linguistics.
Tall, very beautiful.
And despite what some people say,
not broad-backed.
Wait a minute.
You got "Ross Geller and Guest"?
I wasrt invited,
and you got "and Guest"?
Excuse me, I do have to interrupt
on Ross' behalf.
I think the rule applies here.
Since he has a chance
to get on broad-back...
Not broad-back!
Dude, I've seen her. She's like a billboard.
Wait a minute. You're bringing me.
I can't cancel on Joan.
- Why not?
- Did you not hear me?
She's an assistant professor
in the linguistics department.
They're wild.
- Why do you want to come anyway?
- Because...
...she's my cousin.
I mean, we grew up together.
Family, you know?
And all that's important to me.
Okay, all right. I'll take you.
I'll go call Joan.
Oh, that's nice.
Family should be there.
It's her wedding.
Happiest day of her life.
We'll see.
Well, thank you for lunch.
Wait, I thought you paid.
Apparently, we don't pay
for food anymore.
- Do you see what I see?
- It's still there.
Mrs. Braverman must be out.
She could be out of town.
Maybe gone for months.
By then, it may spoil.
She can't come back to bad cheesecake.
- It could kill her.
- Don't want that.
We're protecting her.
- We'll take it.
- But quick.
- Why?
- I hear her in there.
Go! Go! Go!
Do you think it's inappropriate to wear
a white, lacy dress to a wedding?
- Yes.
- Excellent.
Oh, my God, that's David.
- Who?
- David, the scientist guy.
David that I was in love with.
Who went to Russia
and broke my heart, David.
Oh, my God!
Say their name enough,
they turn around.
Phoebe.
David.
What are you doing?
Arert you supposed to be in Russia?
I'm just in town for a conference.
God, you look phenomenal.
Well...
Yeah.
You look great too.
Did you get a haircut?
Yeah. Well, I got like 30 of them.
Look, I got a confession to make.
I was hoping to run into you here.
I didn't know if I should call.
I was only in town a few days...
...and I didn't want to intrude
on your life.
I really wanted to see you...
...but I didn't know
if you wanted to see me.
Of course I would want to see you.
I think about you all the time.
Really? Because I think about you
all the time.
There's a statue in Minsk
that reminds me of you so much.
It's actually of Lenin...
...but, you know, at certain angles...
Anyway, do you want
to have dinner tonight?
Yes.
Oh, no!
- What?
- I can't.
I can't believe I have plans.
Can you do it tomorrow?
No, I have to go in a few hours.
I have to be on the redeye.
Listen, next time you're in Minsk...
Phoebe? Can I talk to you
for a second?
What are you doing?
I have plans with Joey.
So? He'll understand.
No, he won't.
And that's not even the point.
I made a whole speech about how
you do not cancel plans with friends.
And now just because, potentially,
the love of my life...
...returns from Russia
for one night...
...I should change my beliefs?
I should change my beliefs!
No. If I don't have my principles,
I don't have anything.
You're so strong.
Or I should rush through dinner
with Joey and meet David at 9.
Oh, my God, that is so good!
I'm full. And yet I know
if I stop eating this...
...l'll regret it.
Hey, what have you got there?
Oh, it's...
It's tofu cake. Want some?
What are you doing tonight?
Dude. Dude.
Sorry.
I got plans with Phoebe.
Really? Monica said
she had a date at 9.
- What? Tonight?
- That's what Monica said.
After that speech, she makes a date on
the same night she has plans with me?
She's trying to pull a fast one
on Big Daddy.
- Now, if you'll excuse me...
- Dude, dude!
If I took off my pants right now,
how would you feel?
Like your cousin Glenn.
Here, I think this is us.
Limited seating, my ass.
Let's see who made the cut.
Hi. I'm Monica Geller.
- How do you know the bride and groom?
- I worked with Frannie.
Used to work with her. Used to.
I'm a relative
and I didn't get invited.
A blood relative. Blood.
Stop saying "blood" to strangers.
From the ages of 7 to 9, we were
inseparable, and I didn't even get invited!
Then why are you here?
- I'm my brother's date.
- Hey, I had a date, okay?
Joan Tedeschi, the linguist.
So how about you?
How do you know the happy couple?
We went to college with both of them.
Now we live next door.
Okay, you're fine.
You know, you would've liked Joan,
she's very pleasant.
There! There! Her back looks like that.
That's not broad, is it?
Come on, Joey, you've got to be ready
to order by now.
You know, I don't I like this table
either. Maybe we should move again.
No, we're staying right here.
Excuse me, we're ready to order.
I don't work here.
Well, then you shouldn't be
walking around.
- Are you guys ready?
- Yes.
I'll have a green salad,
house dressing and water's fine.
And for you, sir?
Yeah. This slow-roasted salmon...
...how slow are we talking?
It's already been roasted.
Oh, then no. Maybe I should hear
the specials again.
We've heard the specials three times.
There's prime rib, mahi-mahi
and a very special lobster ravioli.
- Actually, we're out of the ravioli.
- Well, that changes everything!
You know what, Pheebs?
You were right before.
Friends are so important.
Yeah, I'm very wise. I know.
Know what I really want?
- What?
- Is to have a long, long talk.
You know? Get Joey out on the
open road and really open him up.
- Any progress?
- Yes.
I will have the lobster ravioli.
God, Joey, this is taking forever.
- What's the rush?
- Well...
...I have an appointment.
And it's very important.
What is it?
Well...
...it's a date.
A date? No, you must be mistaken,
because you wouldn't have a date...
...on the same night
you have plans with a friend.
Don't make me feel badly.
No, I'm gonna!
You made me feel really guilty
about going out with that girl.
Like I did something terrible.
Now you're doing the same thing.
It's not! It's totally different!
This is with David.
Remember David, the scientist guy?
He's very special to me.
My girl the other night was special.
She was a scientist too.
- She was?
- Well, she graduated high school.
Whatever. Know what?
He's only here for four
hours and I'm gonna go see him.
- Fine!
- Yeah.
What are you still doing here?
I told you, lobster ravioli!
I was about to leave.
I didn't think you were coming.
I wouldn't have missed this.
Well, I'm very glad you're here.
Oh, you're such a gentleman.
Come on, we're going to my place.
Are you eating the cheesecake
without me?
I will give you $ 100
to whistle right now.
- How can you eat it without me?
- What'll you do?
Tell Monica or Joey?
No, you'd have to tell them everything.
We're dessert stealers.
We're living outside the law.
I don't trust you with this cake.
I got it first,
and I'm taking it back!
- What? Oh, no.
- Oh, yes.
You think I trust you with it?
No, we'll split it.
That's not fair. You had some.
I think Monica would be
very interested to know...
...that you called her cheesecake
"dry and mealy."
What do we use to split it?
All right, pick a half.
Well, this side looks bigger.
But there's more crust on this side.
Maybe if I measure it...
Pick a piece!
- All right, I pick that one.
- It's the smaller piece.
Okay. There you go.
Enjoy your half, my friend.
But that is it.
No sharing, no switching,
and don't come crying to me...
...if you eat your piece too fast.
- You gonna give me some of yours?
- Oh, no.
No switching, no sharing.
And don't come crying to me.
I may just sit here
and have my cake all day.
Just sit here in the hallway
and eat my...
Ross, sweetheart!
Oh, hey, Aunt Millie.
- Isn't it a beautiful wedding?
- Yes, it is.
Every time, on the lips!
Why? Why on the lips?
There's Frannie.
Wort she be happy to see me?
You be nice, all right?
I didn't bring you to ambush her.
Frannie was the one
who showed your Playboys to Mom.
That bitch.
Monica!
What...?
Am I doing here?
Surprised to see me?
Ross brought me.
How do you like that?
Hi, Frannie. Congratulations.
You invite my whole family,
and not me? Why?
Why wouldn't you want me here?
What could I have done?
Stuart!
I believe you know my husband.
So it's really a question
of "who" could you have done.
I hate this, but I have to go.
I can't miss my flight.
I bet there's
another flight to Minsk in...
July.
That's really beautiful.
What does it mean?
"Please clean my beakers."
I don't get out of the lab much.
I thought it meant something else.
Yeah, well, I really actually
wanted to say...
...that.
But I figured I probably shouldn't
because...
...I have to leave.
No, you're right. Don't say it.
I do, though.
I do too.
Well, bye, Phoebe.
Now's not the time, Joey.
You can yell at me tomorrow.
Wait, no, Pheebs.
I'm not gonna yell at you.
I just started thinking
about you and David...
...and I remember how bummed you were
the first time he left.
Oh, Pheebs, come here.
- Are you okay?
- No, I'm not okay.
The only guy I've ever been
crazy about is going to Minsk...
...and I may never see him again.
You could always visit him.
Right. Like they'll let me
have a passport.
Anything I can do? Whatever you need.
Well, now...
...if you achieve distillation of
subatomic particles before he does...
...then he could come back.
I could give it a shot.
Oh, look! There's a piece
that doesn't have floor on it.
- Stick to your side!
- Come on, now!
All right, what are we having?
- Oh, wait, I forgot my wrap.
- Oh, I'll wait here for you.
- I can't go back there!
- Why?
Did you see the way Stuart was staring
at me? I think he still wants me.
- Oh, my God.
- Just go do it!
All right, wait here.
Hi, sweetie! Are you leaving?
- Well...
- Give us a kiss. Come on.
Why? Why on the lips?